Guide to the Graphics collection, 1740-1995 MS2379
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Graphics, 1740-1995; Series 1
  - President Roosevelt addressing Senators., Circa 1905?]; Series 1; 1 photographic print on stereophonic card: stereograph, color; 9 x 18 cm. (Box 38, Folder 7)
    Cataloging notes: "Around the world without leaving your home -- Just like being there."; No Washingtoniana Vertical File number.; Inaugural speech, 1905, by Theodore Roosevelt at the U.S. Capitol.
    Roosevelt, Theodore, 1858-1919 Inauguration, 1905 Pictorial works.; Roosevelt, Theodore, 1858-1919. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00032496; United States Capitol (Washington, D.C.) Pictorial works.; United States Capitol (Washington, D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00631067; 1905 fast; Presidents United States Inauguration Pictorial works.; Inauguration. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01198743; Presidents Inauguration. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01075771; United States. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204155; Pictorial works. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01423874
  - President Roosevelt's inauguration address., Circa 1905?]; Series 1; 1 photographic print on stereophonic card: stereograph, color; 9 x 18 cm. (Box 38, Folder 8)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 1157
    Cataloging notes: "Around the world without leaving your home -- just like being there."; No Washingtoniana Vertical File number.; Inaugural speech, 1905, by Theodore Roosevelt at the U.S. Capitol.
  - President Roosevelt taking the oath., Circa 1905?]; Series 1; 1 photographic print on stereophonic card: stereograph, color; 9 x 18 cm. (Box 38, Folder 9)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 1158
    Cataloging notes: "Around the world without leaving your home -- just like being there."; No Washingtoniana Vertical File number.; Theodore Roosevelt taking the Presidential oath of office, 1905, at the United States Capitol.
  - Opening address of inauguration ceremonies., Circa 1905?]; Series 1; 1 photographic print on stereophonic card: stereograph, color; 9 x 18 cm. (Box 38, Folder 10)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 1159
    Cataloging notes: No Washingtoniana Vertical File number.; Theodore Roosevelt's inauguration, 1905, at the U.S. Capitol.
  - U.S. Treasury Building: American scenery, Washington, D.C., Circa [189-?]; Series 1; 1 photographic print on stereophonic card: stereograph, black and white; 9 x 18 cm. (Box 38, Folder 11)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 1161
    Cataloging notes: "From Phineas Kelly, Crockery and Glassware ... Saco, Maine."; No Washingtoniana Vertical File number.; Front of the U.S. Treasury Building at 15th and Pennsylvania Avenue, N.W., Washington, D.C.; building in use since 1838.
  - U.S. Treasury., Circa 189-?]; Series 1; 1 photographic print on stereophonic card: stereograph, black and white; 9 x 18 cm. (Box 38, Folder 12)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 1162
    Cataloging notes: No Washingtoniana Vertical File number.; United States Treasury Department building at 15th and Pennysylvania Ave., N.W., Washington, D.C. building in use since 1838.
  - U.S. Treasury buildings, east or principal front: Washington city views., Circa [189-?]; Series 1; 1 photographic print on stereophonic card: stereograph, black and white; 9 x 18 cm. (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 1163
    Cataloging notes: "No. 1993."; No Washingtoniana Vertical File number.; United States Treasury building at 15th and Pennsylvania Ave., N.W., Washington, D.C.; building in use since 1838; carriages in front of building; real estate signs posted in foreground.
  - John Henry Dale Jr.: chairman of Board, S.E. House., Circa [1943]; Series 1; 1 photographic print: black and white; 18 x 13 cm. (Box 38, Folder 14)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 1168
    Cataloging notes: John Henry Dale, Jr., with pipe.; No Washingtoniana Vertical File number.
    Dale, John Henry.; African Americans Washington (D. C.) Portraits.
  - Haile Selassie daughters by Scurlock Studio., Circa [1947]; Series 1; 1 photographic print: black and white; 21 x 26 cm. (Box 38, Folder 15)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 1169
    Cataloging notes: No Washingtoniana Vertical File number.; Daughters of Haile Selassie, Emperor of Ethiopia, at a Howard University graduation in 1947.
    Haile Selassie I, Emperor of Ethiopia, 1892-1975 Family Portraits.; Haile Selassie I, Emperor of Ethiopia, 1892-1975. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00034121; Howard University Pictorial works.; Howard University. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00533680; Families. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01728849; Pictorial works. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01423874; Portraits. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01423831
  - Haile Selassie sons by Scurlock Studio., Circa [1947]; Series 1; 1 photographic print: black and white; 21 x 26 cm. (Box 38, Folder 16)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 1170
    Cataloging notes: No Washingtoniana Vertical File number.; Sons of Haile Selassie, Emperor of Ethiopia, at a Howard University graduation in 1947.
  - [Howard University Rankin Chapel, end of services]., Circa [1946]; Series 1; 1 photographic print: black and white; 26 x 21 cm. (Box 38, Folder 17)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 1171
    Cataloging notes: No Washingtoniana Vertical File number.; Title from pencil notation on verso of photographic printing.; Group of people coming out of the Rankin Chapel on the campus of Howard University, Washington, D.C.
  - [Howard University choir exiting from the Rankin Chapel]., Circa [1946]; Series 1; 1 photographic print: black and white; 21 x 26 cm. (Box 38, Folder 18)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 1172
    Cataloging notes: No Washingtoniana Vertical File number.; Title from pencil notation on verso of photographic printing.; Choir leaving the Rankin Chapel at Howard University in Washington, D.C.
  - [Freedmen's Hospital, main operating room, appendectomy] by Fletcher Foto., Circa [194-?]; Series 1; 1 photographic print: black and white; 21 x 26 cm. (Box 38, Folder 19)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 1173
    Cataloging notes: No Washingtoniana Vertical File number.; Title from pencil notation on verso of photographic printing.; Six people performing an operation in the main operating room at Freedmen's Hospital.
  - [Freedmen's Hospital nurses] by Fletcher Foto., Circa [194-?]; Series 1; 1 photographic print: black and white; 21 x 26 cm. (Box 38, Folder 20)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 1174
    Cataloging notes: Title from pencil notation on verso of photographic printing.; Nurses Elizabeth Sanchez and Bertha Luster drawing blood from female patient at Freedmen's Hospital in Washington, D.C.; No Washingtoniana Vertical File number.
    Sa??nchez, Elizabeth Portraits.; Luster, Bertha Portraits.; Freedmen's Hospital (Washington, D.C.) Pictorial works.; Hospitals Washington (D.C.) Pictorial works.; African Americans Washington (D.C.) Pictorial works.; Sanchez, Elizabeth Portraits.
  - [Bureau of engraving receiving paper in Wetting Division]., Circa [194-?]; Series 1; 1 photographic print: black and white; 22 x 26 cm. (Box 38, Folder 21)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 1175
    Cataloging notes: No Washingtoniana Vertical File number.; Title from dealer's notes.; Two men working in the U.S. Bureau of Engraving in Washington, D.C.
    United States. Bureau of Engraving and Printing Pictorial works.; United States. Bureau of Engraving and Printing. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00539252; African Americans Washington (D.C.) Pictorial works.; African Americans. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00799558; Washington (D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204505; Pictorial works. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01423874
  - [REPRO march on Washington against lynching]., Circa 1946; Series 1; 1 photographic print: black and white; 26 x 21 cm. (Box 38, Folder 22)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 1176
    Cataloging notes: No Washingtoniana Vertical File number.; Title from dealer's notes.; Anti-lynching march on Washington, 1946; view of Lincoln Memorial, a procession going by with banner; crowd around the Lincoln memorial.
    African Americans Washington (D.C.) Pictorial works.; Civil rights demonstrations Washington (D.C.) Pictorial works.; Lincoln Memorial (Washington, D.C.) Pictorial works.; African Americans. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00799558; Civil rights demonstrations. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00862704; Lincoln Memorial (Washington, D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00999000; Washington (D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204505; Pictorial works. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01423874
  - [Dr. Russell W. Brown, Dir. George Washington Carver Foundation, Dr. J. Henry Smith, Exc. Sec. of Carver Foundation] photograph by Loris C. Boone., Circa [194-?]; Series 1; 1 photographic print: black and white; 21 x 26 cm. (Box 38, Folder 23)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 1177
    Cataloging notes: Title from dealer's notes.; Dr. Russell W. Brown and Dr. Henry Smith study the George Washington Carver postage stamp with several women, probably in Washington, D.C.; No Washingtoniana Vertical File number.
    Brown, Russell W. Portraits.; Smith, J. Henry Portraits.; Carver, George Washington, 1864?-1943 Pictorial works.; African Americans Washington (D.C.) Pictorial works.
  - [Joe Louis in army uniform] by photographer, Club Crystal Caverns., Circa [between 1943 and 1946]; Series 1; 1 photographic print in paper folder: black and white; 13 x 18 cm. (Box 38, Folder 24)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 1178
    Cataloging notes: Title from dealer's notes.; Joe Louis in army uniform seated at a table with a woman; man and women seated at a table in background. In green paper illustrated folder of the Club Crystal Caverns, 2001 Eleventh St., N.W., Washington, D.C.; No Washingtoniana Vertical File number.
    Louis, Joe, 1914-1981 Portraits.; Club Crystal Caverns (Washington, D.C.) Pictorial works.; African Americans Washington (D.C.) Pictorial works.
  - [Joe Louis signature] by photographer, Club Crystal Caverns., Circa [between 1943 and 1946]; Series 1; 1 photographic print in paper folder: black and white; 13 x 18 cm. (Box 38, Folder 25)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 1179
    Cataloging notes: Title from dealer's notes.; Unidentified man and woman at a table at Club Crystal Caverns, 2001 Eleventh St., N.W. Washington, D.C. Ink signature of Joe Louis on face of photographic printing.; No Washingtoniana Vertical File number.
    Club Crystal Caverns (Washington. D.C.) Pictorial works.; African Americans Washington (D.C.) Pictorial works.
  - The Agriculture Department: views of Washington and vicinity., Circa [189-?]; Series 1; 1 photographic print on stereophonic card: stereograph, black and white; 9 x 18 cm (Box 38, Folder 26)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 1180
  - Agricultural grounds, Washington, D.C.: standard series., Circa [189?]; Series 1; 1 photographic print on stereophonic card: stereograph, black and white; 11 x 18 cm (Box 38, Folder 27)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 1181
    Cataloging notes: No Washingtoniana Vertical File number.; View of Department of Agriculture building in Washington, D.C.; statue and many shrubs in foreground.
  - Agriculture Department, Washington, D.C., general view., Circa [189-?]; Series 1; 1 photographic print on stereophonic card: stereograph, black and white; 9 x 18 cm (Box 38, Folder 28)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 1182
    Cataloging notes: No Washingtoniana Vertical File number.; Side view of the Department of Agriculture Building in Washington, D.C.; built in 1868 between 12th and 14th Streets, N.W.; conservatory attached to the building in foreground; woman seated in foreground.
  - Green house, Agricultural Department: American scenery, Washington, D.C., Circa [189-?]; Series 1; 1 photographic print on stereophonic card: stereograph, black and white; 9 x 18 cm (Box 38, Folder 29)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 1183
    Cataloging notes: "No. 44."; No Washingtoniana Vertical File number.; Exterior of U.S. Department of Agriculture greenhouse.
  - American views, metropolitan and suburban scenery, Washington, D.C.: U.S. Botanical Garden by W.M. Chase., Circa [189-?]; Series 1; 1 photographic print on stereophonic card: stereograph, black and white; 9 x 18 cm. (Box 38, Folder 30)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 1184
    Cataloging notes: "No. 1206."; No Washingtoniana Vertical File number.; Large plants growing in the United States Botanic Garden conservatory.
  - Conservatory, Botanical Gardens by E. Totherick, photograph., Circa [189-?]; Series 1; 1 photographic print on stereophonic card: stereograph, hand color; 9 x 18 cm. (Box 38, Folder 31)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 1185
    Cataloging notes: No Washingtoniana Vertical File number.; Inside the greenhouses at the United States Botanic Garden, Washington, D.C.
    United States Botanic Garden Pictorial works.; Photography, Stereographic.
  - Interior of U.S. Conservatory, Botanic Garden, Washington., Circa 189-?]; Series 1; 1 photographic print on stereophonic card: stereograph, black and white; 9 x 18 cm. (Box 38, Folder 32)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 1186
    Cataloging notes: No Washingtoniana Vertical File number.; Inside the greenhouses of the U.S> Botanic Garden in Washington, D.C.
  - New State Dept.., Circa [189-?]; Series 1; 1 photographic print on stereophonic card: stereograph, black and white; 9 x 18 cm. (Box 38, Folder 33)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 1187
    Cataloging notes: No Washingtoniana Vertical File number.; Building of the U.S. State Department, 1875-1947,at 17th and Pennsylvania Ave. N.W., now Old Executive Office Building; fence and shrubs in foreground.
  - Horticultural building: S.E. forcing room., Circa [189-?]; Series 1; 1 photographic print on stereophonic card: stereograph, black and white; 9 x 18 cm (Box 39, Folder 1)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 1188
    Cataloging notes: No Washingtoniana Vertical File number.; Plants growing in the Agriculture Department greenhouses in Washington, D.C.
  - Botanical gardens, century plant: Washington, D.C. and vicinity by G.W. Woodward., Circa [189-?]; Series 1; 1 photographic print on stereophonic card: stereograph, black and white; 9 x 18 cm. (Box 39, Folder 2)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 1189
    Cataloging notes: "1477."; No Washingtoniana Vertical File number.; Century plant in the U.S. Botanic Garden, Washington, D.C.
  - [Library of Congress interior] by Jas. Perdu., Circa [189-?]; Series 1; 1 photographic print: black and white; 22 x 18 cm. (Box 39, Folder 3)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 1190
    Cataloging notes: No Washingtoniana Vertical File number.; Title from dealer's notes.; Interior staircase of the Jefferson Building of the Library of Congress, Washington, D.C.
  - Soldiers' Home., Circa [189-?]; Series 1; 1 photographic print: black and white; 18 x 23 cm. (Box 39, Folder 4)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 1191
    Cataloging notes: No Washingtoniana Vertical File number.; Main building of Soldiers' Home Washington, D.C. Established in 1851 as the Military Asylum; name changed in 1859 to Soldiers' Home and in 1972 to the United States Soldiers' and Airmen's Home. Cannon shown in foreground.
  - [Thomas Circle]., Circa [ 1900]; Series 1; 1 photographic print: black and white; 18 x 23 cm. (Box 39, Folder 5)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 1192
    Cataloging notes: No Washingtoniana Vertical File number.; Title is from dealer's notes.; Thomas Circle in Washington, D.C.; shows horse-drawn carriages in street; shows statue of George Henry Thomas.
  - [Library of Congress exterior]., Circa [189-?]; Series 1; 1 photographic print: black and white; 18 x 23 cm. (Box 39, Folder 6)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 1193
    Cataloging notes: No Washingtoniana Vertical File number.; Title from dealer's notes.; Exterior of the Jefferson Building of the Library of Congress; built 1889-1897. Two people shown in the street in front.
  - Conservatory: Agriculture Department, Washington, D.C., Circa [189-?]; Series 1; 1 photographic print on stereophonic card: stereograph, black and white; 10 x 18 cm (Box 39, Folder 7)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 1194
    Cataloging notes: No Washingtoniana Vertical File number.; Conservatory with large plants shown in the Department of Agriculture conservatory in Washington, D.C.
  - Post Office, Washington., Circa [189-?]; Series 1; 1 photographic print on stereophonic card: stereograph, black and white; 9 x 18 cm. (Box 39, Folder 8)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 1195
    Cataloging notes: No Washingtoniana Vertical File number.; U.S. General Post Office, built between 1839 and 1844, located between 7th and 8th and E and F Streets, N.W., in Washington, D.C.
  - Post Office., Circa [189-?]; Series 1; 1 photographic print on stereophonic card: stereograph, black and white; 9 x 18 cm. (Box 39, Folder 9)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 1196
    Cataloging notes: No Washingtoniana Vertical File number.; U.S. General Post Office in Washington, D.C.; built between 1839 and 1844, located between 7th and 8th Streets and E and F Streets, N.W., Washington, D.C. Four men shown standing in front.
  - Post Office, north front., Circa 189-?]; Series 1; 1 photographic print on stereophonic card: stereograph, black and white; 9 x 18 cm. (Box 39, Folder 10)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 1197
    Cataloging notes: North front of the U.S. General Post Office in Washington, D.C.; built between 1839 and 1844, located between 7th and 8th and E and F Streets, N.W., Washington, D.C.; two carriages shown in street.; No Washingtoniana Vertical File number.
  - The State Department: American scenery, Washington, D.C., Circa 189-?]; Series 1; 1 photographic print on stereophonic card: stereograph, black and white; 9 x 18 cm. (Box 39, Folder 11)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 1199
    Cataloging notes: No Washingtoniana Vertical File number.; U.S. State Department Building, now Executive Office Building, in Washington, D.C., 17th and Pennsylvania Ave., N.W. Occupied by State Department 1875-1947. Fence and gate shown in foreground.
  - Louise Home by E. Totherick, photograph., Circa [189-?]; Series 1; 1 photographic print on stereophonic card: stereograph, black and white; 9 x 18 cm. (Box 39, Folder 12)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 1200
    Cataloging notes: No Washingtoniana Vertical File number.; Louise Home in Washington, D.C.; front view; opened 1871 for as a home for impoverished women of good character; located at 1500 Massachusetts Avenue.
    Louise Home (Washington, D.C.) Pictorial works.; Louise Home (Washington, D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00656036; Pictorial works. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01423874
  - War Department: Washington, D.C., the "best" series., Circa 187-?]; Series 1; 1 photographic print on stereophonic card: stereograph, black and white; 9 x 18 cm. (Box 39, Folder 13)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 1201
    Cataloging notes: No Washingtoniana Vertical File number.; U.S. War Department building, near Lafayette Square, occupied circa 1820-1880. Trees in foreground.
    United States. War Department Pictorial works.; United States. War Department. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01853257; Pictorial works. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01423874
  - The National Observatory: American scenery, Washington, D.C., Circa 188-?]; Series 1; 1 photographic print on stereophonic card: stereograph, black and white; 9 x 18 cm. (Box 39, Folder 14)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 1202
    Cataloging notes: No Washingtoniana Vertical File number.; Old Naval Observatory in Foggy Bottom, in use as observatory, 1844-1893; front view.
    United States Naval Observatory Pictorial works.; United States Naval Observatory. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00528874; Astronomical observatories Pictorial works.; Astronomical observatories. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00819649; Pictorial works. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01423874
  - Navy Department: American views., Circa [187-?]; Series 1; 1 photographic print on stereophonic card: stereograph, black and white; 10 x 18 cm. (Box 39, Folder 15)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 1203
    Cataloging notes: No Washingtoniana Vertical File number.; United States Department of the Navy building, in Washington, D.C. Front of building with carriage in the street. Building occupied by the Department of the Navy before 1875.
    United States. Navy Department Pictorial works.; United States. Navy Department. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01853218; Pictorial works. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01423874
  - View of the U.S. Capitol., Circa [189-?]; Series 1; 1 photographic print on stereophonic card: stereograph, black and white; 9 x 18 cm. (Box 39, Folder 16)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 1204
    Cataloging notes: No Washingtoniana Vertical File number.; View of the U.S. Capitol in Washington, D.C.; row of houses in foreground.
  - National Soldier's Cemetery, Arlington photographed by Kilburn Brothers., Circa [189-?]; Series 1; 1 photographic print on stereophonic card: stereograph, black and white; 9 x 18 cm. (Box 39, Folder 17)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 1205
    Cataloging notes: "No. 324."; No Washingtoniana Vertical File number.; View of Arlington Cemetery in Arlington, Virginia; sign with poem in foreground; graves in background.
    Arlington National Cemetery (Va.) Pictorial works.; Cemeteries Virginia Arlington Pictorial works.
  - Tomb of Washington, Mount Vernon photographed by Kilburn Brothers., Circa [189-?]; Series 1; 1 photgraphic print on stereophonic card: stereograph, black and white; 9 x 17 cm. (Box 39, Folder 18)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 1206
    Cataloging notes: "No. 916."; No Washingtoniana Vertical File number.; Front view of the tomb of George Washington at Mount Vernon, Virginia.
  - LaFayette Park: Washington City, D.C. by G.W. Woodward., Circa [189-?]; Series 1; 1 photographic print on stereophonic card: stereograph, black and white; 9 x 18 cm. (Box 39, Folder 19)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 1207
    Cataloging notes: "1483."; No Washingtoniana Vertical File number.; Lafayette Park in Washington, D.C.; fence shown in foreground.
    Lafayette Park (Washington, D.C.) Pictorial works.; Washington (D.C.) Lafayette Park. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01317373; Pictorial works. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01423874
  - Entire dome of U.S. Capitol, Brumidi: Washington City and vicinity., Circa 189-?]; Series 1; 1 photographic print on stereophonic card: stereograph, black and white; 9 x 18 cm. (Box 39, Folder 20)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 1208
    Cataloging notes: No Washingtoniana Vertical File number.; Canopy of the dome of the U.S. Capitol, painted by Constantino Brumidi.
  - The Rogers bronze door: views of Washington and vicinity photographed by J.F. Jarvis., Circa [189-?]; Series 1; 1 photographic print on stereophonic card: stereograph, black and white; 10 x 18 cm (Box 39, Folder 21)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 1209
    Cataloging notes: No Washingtoniana Vertical File number.; Bronze doors designed by Randolph Rogers; occupies the entrance to East Portico in the U.S. Capitol.
  - Panoramic view from the Capitol, south-east: American views, Washington, D.C., Circa [189-?]; Series 1; 1 photographic print on stereophonic card: stereograph, black and white; 9 x 18 cm. (Box 39, Folder 22)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 1210
    Cataloging notes: "10948."; No Washingtoniana Vertical File number.; View of Washington, D.C. from the U.S. Capitol.
  - National and metropolitan scenery, Washington, D.C.: American views by W.M. Chase., Circa 189-?]; Series 1; 1 photographic print on stereophonic card: stereograph, black and white; 9 x 18 cm. (Box 39, Folder 23)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 1211